

SIDHARTH JUYAL

E-mail: sid.juyal.34@gmail.com

Phone: +91 6397223689 LinkedIn: <u>Sidharth-Juyal</u> Github: <u>Sidharth-Juyal</u> YouTube: <u>Winter-Nights</u>

CODING PROFILE

Leetcode: sidharth juyal

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hard-working programmer and a meticulous frontend web developer with a flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time with over 1 year of front-end experience and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach.

TECHNICAL COMPETENCIES

C++ | HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Github | Bootstrap5 | Figma | Adobe Premiere Pro

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Optimistic | Punctual | Calm and Composed | Team Player | Active Listener

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

Singing | Football | Swimming | Videography | Playing Guitar

LANGUAGES KNOWN

English | Hindi | Garhwali

PERSONAL DETAILS

Mother's Name: Mrs. Asha Juyal Father' Name: Mr. Ganesh Juyal

D.O.B.: 30/04/2001

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Engineering in Computer Science | Chandigarh University, Gharuan

Session: 2019-2023 | Score: 8.01 CGPA

Intermediate (CBSE) | DAV Public School, Kotdwara, Uttarakhand

Session: 2017-2018 | Percentage: 83.2%

Matriculation (CBSE) | DAV Public School, Kotdwara, Uttarakhand

Session: 2015-2016 | Percentage: 90.25%

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOLAR SECURE SOLUTIONS | Frontend Intern

13th April 2022 - 15th June 2022

- Learned about latest technologies required for frontend web development.
- Project Built: Documentation catalogue for solar panels and machineries.

EDUREKA | Frontend Intern

18th May 2022 - Present

 Currently Learning about MERN stack technologies, Project in progress: Edureka Educational IMS.

PROJECTS

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

- Highly responsive and stunning UI/UX CV website.
- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, vanilla Javascript.
- Hosting (Github): https://sidharthjuyal.github.io/

MICROSOFT/ FACEBOOK CLONE

- Highly responsive Login page clone of microsoft and facebook.
- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, vanilla Javascript and TailwindCSS.
- Hosting (Github): https://github.com/sidharthjuyal/tailwind-css/

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGNS

- Created 5 real-time projects necessary to complete the freeCodeCamp.
- Hosting (Github): https://github.com/sidharthjuyal/freecodecamp-responsive-web-design.

CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS

- Benefits of Bootstrap, (Coursera)
- C++ Masterclass, (Lernen Hub Academy)
- Programming Fundamentals, (Duke University)
- Responsive Web Designs, (FreeCodeCamp)
- Programming fundamentals with HTML, CSS and JS, (Duke University)

EXTRA CURRICULAR & CO-CURRICULAR ACHIEVEMENTS

- University level solo singing winner
- Youtube Channel with over 40k+ views